alexnld.com 2019-07-06

# Privacy Policy | Alexnld.com

1.1 Definition of personal data.

Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data.Personal data does not include data that has been irreversibly anonymized or aggregated so that it can no longer enable us, whether in combination with other information or otherwise, to identify you.

Here is a description of the types of personal data we may collect and how we may use it:

1.2 What Personal Data We Collect

Depending on the products and services you choose, we collect different kinds of personal data from or about you.

  * Data you provide

We collect the personal data you provide when you create an account to use our products and services or otherwise interact with us, such as when you fill in account information, contact us, participate in an online survey, use our online help or online chat tool.

  * Data from your terminalequiments

  1. ** ** Photos/ Media/ File  
Our app can use files or data stored on your device.If you want to prevent our app from accessing to your phone data ,you can reset  your permission on your phone.After obtaining your permission, Photos/Media/Files access may include the ability to:  
① Read the contents of your USB storage (such as SD card).  
② Addcontents to your USB storage  
③ Format external storage  
④ Mount or unmount external storage
  2. Local storage  
We may collect and store information (including personal data) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.
  3. 3\. Camera  
You can upload photos when you comment by online services. So, we should collect images and other information from your device’s camera and photos. For example, you will not be able to upload photos from your camera roll unless we can access your camera or photosbyyour permission.  
4\. Unique application numbers  
Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to website when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers, such as for automatic updates.

  * Data about purchase

If you make a purchase, we collect personal data in related with the purchase. This data includes your purchase data, such as your mail of paypal,user name,shipping address and other authentication information, as well as billing, shipping, and contact details.

  * Data about improvingour services and products

When you visit our websites, we may collect data about the type of device you use, your device’s unique identifier, the IP address of your device, your operating system, the type of Internet browser that you use, usage information, diagnostic information, and location information from or about the computers, phones, or other devices on which you install or access our products or services. Where available, our services may use GPS, your IP address, and other technologies to determine a device’s approximate location to allow us to improve our products and services.

1.3 How We Use Your Personal Data

Generally speaking, we use personal data to provide, improve, and develop our products and services, to communicate with you, to offer you targeted advertisements and services, and to protect us and our customers.

Alexnld.com determines and controls how to process your personal data as data controller for the following purposes:

  * Providing, improving, and developing our products and services

We use your personal data to help us provide, improve, and develop our products and services. This may includes using personal data for purposes such as complete shopping process,improving the users experiences,data analysis, research, and audits. Such processing is based on your prior express consent or our legitimate interest in offering you products and services.We encourage you to read those rules of privacy policy carefully before participating.If you no longer wish to agree above services we provide,please contact us to opt-out.

  * Communicating with you

Subject to your prior express consent, we may use personal data to send you marketing communications in relation to our own products and services, communicate with you about your account or transactions, and inform you about our policies and terms. If you no longer wish to receive email communications for directly marketing purposes, please contact us to opt-out. We also may use your data to process and respond to your requests when you contact us. If you no longer wish to agree above services we provide, please contact us to opt-out.

  * Offering and measuring targeted advertisements and services

Subject to your prior express consent, we may use your personal data to personalize your experience with our products and services and on third-party websites and applications and to determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. You are free to choose whether receive promotion information or not. If you no longer wish to agree above services we provide, please send e-mail to us to opt-out or choose”unsubscribe” to opt out in those e-mails.

  * Promoting safety and security

Subject to your prior express consent,we may use some technology measures to protect your personal data for helping verify accounts and user normal activities, as well as to promote data safety and security, such as by monitoring fraud and investigating suspicious or potentially illegal activity or violations of our terms or policies. Such processing is based on our legitimate interest in helping ensure the safety of our products and services.

1.4 How We Store Your Personal Data

We may take technology measures to make sure your personal data record is complete and accurate,such as cookies and similar technologies.And Subject to your prior express consent,we may store our processing record of your personal data for ten years.

## Your Rights

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal data is accurate, complete, and up to date. Based on protection for your privacy，your have the following rights:

You have the right to contactus to know whether or not your personal data is being processed, and, where that is the case, access to the personal data and information,including but not limited to the purposes of the processing and the categories of personal data concerned.  
You have the right to contact us to correct or delete your inaccurate personal data concerning. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, you are also free to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.  
You have the right to obtain from usthe erasure of personal data concerning yourself.  
You have the right to contact usto set the restriction of processing, which limited our processing authorities  
You have the right to receive the personal data you provide in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit those data to a third party.  
You have the right to contact us to make your objection on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time to processing of personal data  
You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing,including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you. When you need to realize this right, please contact us to offer help.  
To protect the privacy and the security of your personal data, we may request data from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access such data, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal data we maintain. There are instances where applicable laws or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide or delete some or all of the personal data that we maintain.  
You may contact us to exercise your rights. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

3.1 Checking your details

How can I check my personal data  
You can check your personal data via entering “My Account”.

Deleting your Information  
Please cantact us when you find it necessary to delete your imformation :

Personal data for providing, improving, and developing our products and services. If this type of data is deleted, your account will be close because your account can not be used normally without this type of data.  
Personal data that we use to communicate with you. If this type of data is deleted, we will be unable to contact you. Please make your decisions cautiously.  
Personal data to offer and measure targeted advertisements and services. If this type of data is deleted, you will not receive the latest marketing news and personalized shopping services.  
Personal data relating to promoting safety and security. If this type of data is deleted, your account will be strongly threatened that you may not use your account normally.

If you delete your data, we have no obligation to retain your data, and we may delete any or all of your data without liability. However, we may retain data related to you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, if required by law, or for legitimate purposes, such as analysis of non-personal data, account recovery, auditing our records, and enforcing our rights and obligations under our agreements.

## Disclosure of Personal Data

We make certain personal data available to strategic partners that work with us to provide our products and services or help us market to customers. Personal data will only be shared by us with these companies in order to provide or improve our products, services, and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their own marketing purposes without your prior express consent.

5.1 Service Providers  
We share personal data with companies that provide services on behalf of us, such as website hosting, email services, marketing, sponsoring of sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions, auditing, fulfilling customer orders, data analytics, providing customer service, and conducting customer research and satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your data and may be located wherever we operate.

5.2 Corporate Affiliates and Corporate Business Transactions

We may share personal data with affiliated companies and business partners. In the event of a merger, reorganization, acquisition, joint venture, assignment, spin-off, transfer, or sale or disposition of all or any portion of our business, including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings, we may transfer any and all personal data to the relevant third party.

5.3 Legal Compliance and Security

It may be necessary—by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence—for us to disclose personal data. We may also disclose personal data if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.  
We may also disclose personal data if we determine in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our rights and pursue available remedies, enforce our terms and conditions, investigate fraud, or protect our operations or users.

5.4 Legal Basis For The Processing of Personal Data from EEA Residents

It may be necessary—by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence—for us to disclose personal data. We may also disclose personal data if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.  
If you reside within the European Economic Area (EEA), our processing of your personal data will be justified if one of the following conditions is satisfied:

Whenever we obtain your consent;

Whenever the processing of your personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract between you and us or for taking any pre-contractual steps upon your request;

Where the processing is necessary for us to comply with a legal obligation;

Where the processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests;

Where the processing is necessary for legal and reasonable causes (under this situation we will specifically explain the details)

## Data processed by Third Party

7.1 Third party’s previous authorization to us

Facebook, Twitter, Google, VK  
When you login in by your account via Facebook, Twitter, Google, VK at Alexnld.com, we are available to obtain your login in information automatically because of these third parties have previously authorized us to collect your information in order to help you login in conveniently. To protect your information better, we sincerely recommend you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policy provided by these third parties before you login in through your account registered at their websites. Consequently, please note that you should also take steps to protect yourself, especially online. Do not share your password with anyone else. Also remember to sign out of the website and close your browser window when you have finished your work. If you really mind providing us with your personal data through the previous authorization, you may register a new account at Alexnld.com.

Paypal  
If you choose to pay online through “ Check out with Paypal”, please be aware of the fact that once you click the button, you will be link to the website of Paypal. The personal data that you are asked to provide, including your card number, your billing address and your contact information, will be collected and processed by Paypal instead of Alexnld.com, though our trademark/logo can still be seen on the top left corner on that website. We sincerely recommend you to learn about the privacy policy of Paypal and make your choice among different payments cautiously. Alexnld.com should not be liable for your data processing by Paypal when you click the button “ Check out with Paypal”.

7.2 Other Third parties that may reach your information

To provide better products and service for our customers, we may mainly transfer your data to the two types of third parties,

Thirdparty related to Advertising & Marketing——Google、Facebook、Twitter、Amazon、Pinterest、TradeTracker, etc.  
Information of your activities on our website, for example, what products you like to browse, may be transferred to these third parties. You may receive Communication letters on advertising and marketing in your e-mail sent by us and/or selected third parties. You have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. When you do not want to receive advertisements from us and/or selected third parties any more, you should opt-out by contacting us (e-mail) or click on the “unsubscribe” link in any email communications which you receive.

Third-party related to Payment& Delivery——Paypal、Cybersource、 Adyen、 Dlocal、Stripe、Safecharge、Oceanpayment,etc.  
If you make a purchase from our store, your payment and delivery information will be necessary to the trade. Your information may be transferred to third parties above and processed by them. We promise that appropriate or suitable safeguards, for example, encryption technology, will be provided to ensure security of your information This type of persnal date is so important to your purchase activities that we strongly recommend you to think twice when you want to delete or object to the processing of these data.

7.3 About Third party located in a third country

As we has stated above, model contractual clauses or alternative legal bases or binding corporate rules will help protect your information security. Once we notice a third party breach its obligation and infringe your privacy, we will immediately notice it to correct its mistake. If you notice a third party breach its obligation and infringe your privacy owing to Alexnld.com’s mistake, you may contact us to obtain remedies. We promise that appropriate or suitable safeguards, for example, encryption technology, will be provided to ensure security of your information. Our customers have right to obtain copy of those data transferred to a third country. If you need to realize your rights, please contact us.

7.4 About Third-party websites

Our website may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and we do not share your information with them unless your permission or other legal basis authorize us to do so. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. We should not be liable for personal data breach caused by these third-party websites.

## Contact us

Thank you for supporting Alexnld.com.

We are always pleased to hear from our customers (even if it is a complaint). We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied.

Please contact us if you have any questions, comments or complaints if you believe that Alexnld.com has not handled your personal data properly or that it has breached its privacy obligations, your complaint may be directed at Alexnld.com Technology Service Department

at data@alexnld.com

The Technology Service Department will investigate any complaint and notify the individual of the outcome of the investigation within a reasonable period. Alexnld.com has set up Data Protection Officer(DPO) to provide professional analysis about personal data processing. Whenever you need help directly from our DPO, please inform us of your requirement.

If your complaint must be solved immediately while the Technology Service Department has not made a response to you, please do not hesitate to reach the Live Support Service provided by our Customer Service Department. Your complaint will be instantly reported to relevant department and investigated.

You are also free to reach us via E-mail to our representative in EU:

data@alexnld.com

CYLLAR CO., LTD

Athalassas, 38 1st floor, Flat/Office 102 Strovolos,2019, Nicosia, Cyprus

The Alexnld.com Team will spare no effort to protect your rights and solve your problems.
